https://www.jewishcafe.com/guests/help/privacy_statement.jsp?id=0

3:46 am EST
JewishCafe.com Privacy Statement
Welcome to the JewishCafe.com community service (referred to herein as the "Service"), owned and produced by RealCafes.com Inc. (referred to herein as "RealCafes.com"). The Service is made available subject to this Privacy Policy. This statement discloses the privacy practices of RealCafes.com with regard to www.jewishcafe.com only. By using the Service, you agree, without limitation or qualification, to be bound by this Privacy Policy.
Contact information for questions regarding this statement should be directed to:
RealCafes.com Privacy Site Coordinator
RealCafes.com Inc.
18478 Ninth Line
Mount Albert, Ontarioa, L0G 1M0
Canada
support@jewishcafe.com
This policy may be updated from time to time, so please check back periodically.
1. What information of yours does RealCafes.com collect?
In registering for the Service, you provide us with a username, an email address, and complete the Service questionnaire. RealCafes.com collects and posts all your responses to the questionnaire, including the zip code you provide and any photos or images that you post. At the end of the registration process, you may be asked whether you are interested in receiving information about certain topics that may be of interest; RealCafes.com collects your responses to those questions. Also, each time you access the Service, RealCafes.com collects and stores your Internet Protocol (IP) address. Occasionally, the Administrator of the community of which you are a member may send a survey to the community members; if you answer the survey, RealCafes.com collects your survey responses.
2. What are "cookies" and how does RealCafes.com use them?
In addition to the information described above that RealCafes.com collects, we also collect information "anonymously" using "cookies." A cookie is a small text file containing a unique identification number that is transferred from a Web site to the hard drive of your computer so that the Web site may identify you and track your activities on the Web site. This unique number identifies your browser-- but not you -- to RealCafes.com computers whenever you visit the Service. A cookie will not let a Web site know any personally identifiable information about you, such as your real name and address. RealCafes.com does not collect personally identifiable information about any one person using cookies. Because cookies are only text files, they cannot run on your computer, search your computer for other information, or transmit any information to anyone. RealCafes.com generally uses cookies to determine in what state your computer workstation is located. Third party advertising networks for RealCafes.com may issue cookies when serving advertisements.
The use of cookies is now an industry standard, and you will find them used on most major Web sites. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. If you prefer, you can reset your browser either to notify you when you have received a cookie, or to refuse to accept cookies. You should understand that while RealCafes.com does not require you to use cookies, certain areas of the Service will not function properly if you set your browser to not accept cookies. For example, you may have difficulty searching the Service, completing the Service questionnaire, and paying for your Service subscription.
3. What organization is collecting the information?
Information provided by you during your registration for and use of the Service is generally collected and maintained solely by RealCafes.com.
RealCafes.com may run promotions and sweepstakes on the Service. These promotions may be sponsored or co-sponsored by third-parties. Data collected during a promotion is typically shared with the sponsor or co-sponsor. RealCafes.com will inform you at the point of collection whether or not we are sharing your personal data as a result of your participation in a promotion or sweepstakes. If you do not want to have RealCafes.com share your data, you can choose not to participate in the promotion or sweepstakes.
Be aware that RealCafes.com sponsors and other advertisers have links on the Service that take you to other sites that may collect personally identifiable information about you. RealCafes.com hopes that all third parties involved adhere to our policies regarding the privacy of our users. However, this JewishCafe.com Privacy Policy does not cover third party data collection practices, and RealCafes.com does not assume any responsibility for any actions of third parties.
4. How does RealCafes.com use the information it collects?
RealCafes.com uses the username and password you provide at registration only to provide and maintain the Service and your access to the Service. Your email address is used to verify your account and to communicate with you regarding the Service and your use of the Service. RealCafes.com collects and displays on the Service all of the acceptable information you provide in completing the questionnaire, including the zip code you provide and any photos or images you post. Your credit card information is used to collect your subscription fee.
RealCafes.com uses the aggregate user data collected to inform our sponsors as to numbers of people who have certain demographic characteristics and the number of those people who have seen and "clicked" on their advertisement(s). We will also disclose to those third-party sponsors the overall demographics available regarding who saw and "clicked" on their advertisement. No personally identifiable information will be disclosed to these advertisers as part of this process; only information in an aggregate form. In addition, RealCafes.com uses the aggregate data to perform statistical analyses of the collective characteristics and behavior of our registered users and visitors and to measure user demographics.
RealCafes.com may, from time to time, use your information to contact you about changes or enhancements to the Service, and other products and services available on the RealCafes.com Network.
If during the registration process you told RealCafes.com that you were interested in receiving offers or information from selected JewishCafe.com sponsors and advertisers or about certain topics of interest, RealCafes.com may provide your email address to third parties that can provide you with such requested information.
RealCafes.com uses your IP address only in the event of a violation of the Service terms and conditions.
If you enter a sweepstakes or a contest on JewishCafe.com, we will use the information you provided to contact you in the event you win.
In addition, RealCafes.com may be required by law enforcement or judicial authorities to provide information on individual users to the appropriate governmental authorities, and RealCafes.com may reveal information on individual users in order to protect such users' personal safety or the personal safety of others.
5. How can you access, edit or delete your information or remove your account?
RealCafes.com provides JewishCafe.com registered users the ability to access and edit the personal information in their user profiles. To access and edit the majority of your personal information, including your responses to the Service questionnaire and essays; your password; the email address you listed with us; and other profile settings including allowing non-members to view your photo or profile; you must click the "Profile" link at the top of any page inside your account, and then select the information you would like to update or revise. If you would like to change your username you may email the Administrator in your community.
If you would like to close your account, you must email the Administrator in your community or click here for more information.
6. What kinds of security procedures are in place to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of your information?
RealCafes.com has security measures in place to attempt to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of your user data under our control. While our employees have access to information, including your username, password, and credit card information, RealCafes.com has strict rules on its employees to maintain all of this information in strict confidence and not to permit this information to be disseminated to third parties. While we cannot guarantee that loss, misuse or alteration to data will not occur, we make every effort to prevent such unfortunate occurrences. Your credit card number is encrypted prior to transmission.
You are ultimately responsible for the security of your JewishCafe.com username and password. Please take care when using and storing them. RealCafes.com recommends that you do not divulge your password to anyone. You should log out of your browser at the end of each computer session to ensure that others cannot access your personal information and correspondence, especially if you share a computer with someone else or are using a computer in a public place like a library or Internet cafe.
7. What you can do to better protect yourself on the Internet
Know the risks - When you communicate with others online, you should be aware that, when disclosing personal information such as one's actual name, member name, e-mail address, etc., on a Web page, in a newsgroup, chat room or forum, that information may be collected and used by others to send you unsolicited e-mail from other parties, outside RealCafes.com. Some of the e-mail you receive may be useful to you, but some may not.
Educate yourself - Search the Web for as much information as you can about how to protect your privacy.
Use PGP (Pretty Good Privacy) or another encryption program.
8. Google Analytics
RealCafes.com uses Google Analytics to analyze traffic on JewishCafe.com. This service uses cookies to collect anonymous traffic data that is then stored on Google's servers for reporting purposes. This information helps RealCafes.com determine where visitors are coming from and how they use JewishCafe.com. No personally identifiable information is collected by or transferred to Google Analytics. RealCafes.com uses this information to assist in bringing more members who match the same demographics as our members. This information is therefore designed to provide the best possible service for JewishCafe.com visitors and members.
Last updated April 17, 2013
[ home ]
[ safety notes ]
[ contact us ]
[ help ]
[ testimonials ]
[ why sign up? ]
[ events ]
[ become an affiliate ]
[ privacy statement ]
[ sign-on with success ]
[ prices ]
© 1998-2020 JewishCafe.com. All rights reserved.
